Ariel listen to me OO languages it's
a mess. Programming in C is better than
anything they've got over there
[Music]
The syntax might seem much sweeter.
Where objects and subtypes play. But frills like
inheritance. Will only get in the way.
Admire C's simple landscape. Efficiently
dangerous. No templates or fancy pitfalls...
...like java and C++!
Program in C
Pointers, assembly. Manage your memory.
With malloc() and free()
Don't sync your app with runtime plot
Software in C will stay afloat. Do what you
want there. Close to the hardware
Program in C
[Music]
With C all the coders happy,
as it's all procedural
the dudes who .NET ain't happy,
they forgot to call Stream.Dispose().
They like to think they so lucky
the runtime will clean their act. But when you abuse
the memory, you are bottlenecked that's a fact!
Oh well! Program in C!
Program in C!
Nobody's faster. -02's the master,
indubitably!
We what the coders like to roast,
but they don't have a lot to boast!
Pure satisfaction, little abstraction,
Program in C!
Neither exceptions, nor your contention,
Can't bother me!
Windows and Linux demonstrate.
portable code is running great!
There's implementations, for all occasions!
Program in C!
[Music]